A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 368, Folder 8)
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen" Adverse Effects, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 368, Folder 9)
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen" Original Manuscript, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 368, Folder 10)
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen" Reprints, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 1)
- "Acetaminophen: Acetaminophen" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 2)
- "Cancer, Chemical Carcinogenesis: Carcinogenicity of Drugs in Small Animals and Mutagenity in Bacteria: Does it Make Sense? " Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 3)
- "Cancer, Chemical Carcinogenesis: Carcinogenicity of Drugs in Small Animals and Mutagenity in Bacteria: Does it Make Sense? " Manufacturer's Replies, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 4)
- "Cancer, Chemical Carcinogenesis: Carcinogenicity of Drugs in Small Animals and Mutagenity in Bacteria: Does it Make Sense? " Original Manuscript, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 5)
- "Cancer, Chemical Carcinogenesis: Carcinogenicity of Drugs in Small Animals and Mutagenity in Bacteria: Does it Make Sense? " Reprints, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 6)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 7)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 8)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma" Original Manuscript, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 9)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma" Reprints [and Vanceril Inhaler Databook], 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 10)
- "Asthma, Drugs for Beclomethasone Dipropionate (Vanceril) for Asthma" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:18, 1976 August 27 (Box 369, Folder 11)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 369, Folder 12)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 369, Folder 13)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Adverse Effects, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 369, Folder 14)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Original Manuscript, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 369, Folder 15)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Reprints, 18:19, 1976 September 10; 1 of 4 (Box 369, Folder 16)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Reprints, 18:19, 1976 September 10; 2 of 4 (Box 370, Folder 1)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Reprints, 18:19, 1976 September 10; 3 of 4 (Box 370, Folder 2)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Reprints, 18:19, 1976 September 10; 4 of 4 (Box 370, Folder 3)
- "Rheumatism and Arthritis (Chemotherapy): New Drugs for Arthritis" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 4)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography" Basic Source Check-List, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 5)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 6)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography" Original Manuscript, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 7)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography" Reprints, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 8)
- "X-Rays: Computed Tomography" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:19, 1976 September 10 (Box 370, Folder 9)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 1)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 2)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts" Original Manuscript, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 3)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts" Reprints, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 4)
- "Lipids: Margarines and Other Dietary Facts" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 5)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:20, 1976 September 24; 1 of 2 (Box 371, Folder 6)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:20, 1976 September 24; 2 of 2 (Box 371, Folder 7)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 8)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Original Manuscript, 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 9)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Sources: "Check Copy" 18:20, 1976 September 24 (Box 371, Folder 10)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Reprints, 18:20, 1976 September 24; 1 of 2 (Box 372, Folder 1)
- "Cancer Immunology: Immunotherapy for Malignant Disease" Reprints, 18:20, 1976 September 24; 2 of 2 (Box 372, Folder 2)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:21, 1976 October 8; 1 of 2 (Box 372, Folder 3)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:21, 1976 October 8; 2 of 2 (Box 372, Folder 4)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 372, Folder 5)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Original Manuscript, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 372, Folder 6)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Reprints, 18:21, 1976 October 8; 1 of 2 (Box 372, Folder 7)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Reprints, 18:21, 1976 October 8; 2 of 2 (Box 373, Folder 1)
- "Antiseptics: Chlorhexidine and Other Antiseptics" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 373, Folder 2)
- "Diarrhea: Travelers' Diarrhea - New Developments" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 373, Folder 3)
- "Diarrhea: Travelers' Diarrhea - New Developments" Original Manuscript, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 373, Folder 4)
- "Diarrhea: Travelers' Diarrhea - New Developments" Reprints, 18:21, 1976 October 8 (Box 373, Folder 5)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 1 of 3 (Box 373, Folder 6)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 2 of 3 (Box 373, Folder 7)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 3 of 3 (Box 373, Folder 8)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:22, 1976 October 22 (Box 373, Folder 9)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Original Manuscript, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 1 of 2 (Box 374, Folder 1)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Original Manuscript, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 2 of 2 (Box 374, Folder 2)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Adverse Effects, 18:22, 1976 October 22 (Box 374, Folder 3)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Reprints, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 1 of 2 (Box 374, Folder 4)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Reprints, 18:22, 1976 October 22; 2 of 2 (Box 374, Folder 5)
- "Psychopharmacological Agents: Drugs for Psychiatric Disorders" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:22, 1976 October 22 (Box 374, Folder 6)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 374, Folder 7)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 374, Folder 8)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Original Manuscript, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 374, Folder 9)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Reprints, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 375, Folder 1)
- "Amikacin: Amikacin" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:23, 1976 November 5 (Box 375, Folder 2)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 1 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 3)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 2 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 4)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Original Manuscript, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 375, Folder 5)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Reprints, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 1 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 6)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Reprints, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 2 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 7)
- "Osteoporosis: Osteoporosis" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 375, Folder 8)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Basic Source Check-List, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 375, Folder 9)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 1 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 10)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19; 2 of 2 (Box 375, Folder 11)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 1)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Original Manuscript, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 2)
- "Fungal Infections: Drugs for Athlete's Foot and Tinea Cruris" Reprints, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 3)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU) " Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 4)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU) " Manufacturer's Replies, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 5)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU) " Original Manuscript, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 6)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU) " Reprints, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 7)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy: Lomustine (CeeNU) " Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 8)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants" Consultants; M. L. Drafts, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 9)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 10)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants" Original Manuscript, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 11)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants" Reprints, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 12)
- "Nutrition and Diet (Infants): Soy-Based Formula for Infants" Advertising; Package Inserts, 18:24, 1976 November 19 (Box 376, Folder 13)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of frostbite" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:105, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 1)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of frostbite" Original Manuscript, 18:105, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 2)
- "ENVIRONMENTAL HEALTH: Treatment of frostbite" Reprints, 18:105, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 3)
- "EYE DISEASE: Treatment of diabetic retinopathy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:107, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 4)
- "EYE DISEASE: Treatment of diabetic retinopathy" Original Manuscript, 18:107, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 5)
- "EYE DISEASE: Treatment of diabetic retinopathy" Reprints, 18:107, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 6)
- "HEMORRHOIDS: Preparation H; " 18:108, 1976 December 3 (Box 377, Folder 7)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25; [1 of 3] (Box 377, Folder 8)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25; [2 of 3] (Box 378, Folder 1)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy" Consultants: ML Drafts, [3 of 3] 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25; [3 of 3] (Box 378, Folder 2)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25 (Box 378, Folder 3)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer, Chemotherapy: cancer chemotherapy" Original Manuscripts, 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25 (Box 378, Folder 4)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: cancer chemotherapy" Reprints, 18:109, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25 (Box 378, Folder 5)
- "CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY: Cancer, Chemotherapy: cancer chemotherapy" Advertising: Package Inserts, Dec. 17, 1976 [CANCER, CHEMOTHERAPY - CORRECTION: cancer chemotherapy"] 19:20, Feb. 25, 1977, 1976 December 17 1977 February 25 (Box 378, Folder 6)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease" Consultants; ML Drafts, 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 378, Folder 7)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 378, Folder 8)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease" Sources; "Check Copy" 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 378, Folder 9)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease" Reprints, 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 378, Folder 10)
- "PARKINSON'S DISEASE, CHEMOTHERAPY: New drugs for Parkinson's Disease" Advertising: Package Inserts, 18:117, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 1)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 2)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 3)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis" Original Manuscripts, 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 4)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis" Reprints, 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 5)
- "RHEUMATISM & ARTHRITIS (Chemotherapy) Arthropan liquid & other salicylates for Arthritis" Advertising: Package Inserts, 18:119, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 6)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes" Consultants: ML Drafts, 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 7)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes" Manufacturer's Replies, 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 8)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes" Original Manuscripts, 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 9)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes" Reprints, 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 10)
- "ANABOLIC AGENTS: Anabolic steroids for athletes" Advertising: Package Inserts, 18:120, 1976 December 31 (Box 379, Folder 11)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Consultants: Ml Drafts, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 379, Folder 12)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 1)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Adverse Effects, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 2)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Original Manuscript, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 3)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Reprints, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 4)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Prazosin (mini press) for hypertension" Advertising: Package: Inserts, 19:1, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 5)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Prevention of serious infections after splenectomy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:2, 1977 January 14; [1 of 2] (Box 380, Folder 6)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Prevention of serious infections after splenectomy" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:2, 1977 January 14; [2 of 2] (Box 380, Folder 7)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Prevention of serious infections after splenectomy" Original Manuscript, 19:2, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 8)
- "ANTIMICROBIALS, PROPHYLACTIC USE (SURGERY): Prevention of serious infections after splenectomy" Reprints, 19:2, 1977 January 14 (Box 380, Folder 9)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:4, 1977 January 14; [1 of 2] (Box 380, Folder 10)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:4, 1977 January 14; [2 of 2] (Box 380, Folder 11)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:4, 1977 January 14 (Box 381, Folder 1)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" [Sources] 19:4, 1977 January 14 (Box 381, Folder 2)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Original Manuscript, 19:4, 1977 January 14 (Box 381, Folder 3)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Reprints, 19:4, 1977 January 14; [1 of 2] (Box 381, Folder 4)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Reprints, 19:4, 1977 January 14; [2 of 2] (Box 381, Folder 5)
- "ANESTHETICS, LOCAL: Long - Acting Local Anesthetics" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:4, 1977 January 14 (Box 381, Folder 6)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: adverse interactions of drugs" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:5, 1977 January 28 (Box 381, Folder 7)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: adverse interactions of drugs" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:5, 1977 January 28 (Box 381, Folder 8)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: adverse interactions of drugs" Original Manuscript, 19:5, 1977 January 28 (Box 381, Folder 9)
- "DRUG INTERACTION: adverse interactions of drugs" Reprints, 19:5, 1977 January 28 (Box 381, Folder 10)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:13, 1977 February 11; [1 of 2] (Box 381, Folder 11)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:13, 1977 February 11; [2., m of 2] (Box 381, Folder 12)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:13, 1977 February 11 (Box 382, Folder 1)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Original Manuscript, 19:13, 1977 February 11 (Box 382, Folder 2)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Reprints, 19:13, 1977 February 11 (Box 382, Folder 3)
- "ADDICTION (ABUSE - OVERDOSE): Diagnosis & Management of reactions to drug abuse" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:13, 1977 February 11 (Box 382, Folder 4)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Ticarcillin" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:17, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 5)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Ticarcillin" Original Manuscript, 19:17, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 6)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Ticarcillin" Reprints, 19:17, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 7)
- "PENICILLINS, NEW: Ticarcillin" Laboratory Reports, Correspondence 19:17, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 8)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 382, Folder 9)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 1)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies" Original Manuscript, 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 2)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies" Reprints, 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 3)
- "PARASITIC INFECTIONS (Drugs for): Kwell & other drugs for treatment of lice & scabies" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:18, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 4)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 5)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 6)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Sources: "Check Copy", 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 7)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Original Manuscript, 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 8)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Reprints, 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 9)
- "COSMETICS: Drysol for treatment of hyperhidrosis" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:20, 1977 February 25 (Box 383, Folder 10)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:21, 1977 March 11; [1 of 2] (Box 383, Folder 11)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:21, 1977 March 11; [2 of 2] (Box 383, Folder 12)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:21, 1977 March 11 (Box 384, Folder 1)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Original Manuscript, 19:21, 1977 March 11 (Box 384, Folder 2)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Reprints, 19:21, 1977 March 11 (Box 384, Folder 3)
- "HYPERTENSION, THERAPY: Drugs for hypertension" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:21, 1977 March 11 (Box 384, Folder 4)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 5)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 6)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin" Original Manuscript, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 7)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin" Reprints, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 8)
- "DIABETES, THERAPY (PHENFORMIN): Phenformin" Advertising: Package Inserts, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 9)
- "ABORTION: Relative safety of mid-trimester abortion methods" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 10)
- "ABORTION: Relative safety of mid-trimester abortion methods" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 11)
- "ABORTION: Relative safety of mid-trimester abortion methods" Original Manuscript, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 12)
- "ABORTION: Relative safety of mid-trimester abortion methods" Reprints, 19:25, 1977 March 25 (Box 384, Folder 13)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 1)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures" Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 2)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures" Manufacturer's Replies, 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 3)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures" Original Manuscript, 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 4)
- "ANALGESICS: Sedation & analgesia for minor painful procedures" Reprints, 19:26, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 5)
- "HEMOSTATICS: Avitene a new topical hemostatic agent" ["CORRECTION: Sodium in ticarcillin and Carbenicillin"] Consultants: ML Drafts, 19:28, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 6)
- "HEMOSTATICS: Avitene a new topical hemostatic agent" ["CORRECTION: Sodium in ticarcillin and Carbenicillin"] Manufacturer's Replies, 19:28, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 7)
- "HEMOSTATICS: Avitene a new topical hemostatic agent" ["CORRECTION: Sodium in ticarcillin and Carbenicillin"] Original Manuscript, 19:28, 1977 March 25 (Box 385, Folder 8)